(Barry:)Before we start, I just want to
warn you, fencing isn't a joke.
(Barry:)I hope you're not here because
you think it's going to be
like Star Wars.
(Leonard:)That's not why we're here.
(Raj:)Yeah, I'm here
because I think
(Raj:)it's gonna be like
Game of Thrones.
(Howard:)And maybe
a little Princess Bride.
Ooh, ooh! I forgot
about Princess Bride!
That's my answer!
Well, sorry to disappoint you,
but fencing is a serious sport.
If you're not willing
to put in the effort,
you might as well just leave
now.
(Sheldon:)We're not afraid of physical activity.
Yeah.
(Howard:)I already ran 18 miles today.
All right. Let's begin
with some fundamentals.
(Barry:)This is the en
garde position.
Feet are in an "L."
Heels in a straight line.
(Barry:)Elbow is
about a fist
from the rib cage.
(Barry:)Notice my dominant
leg faces forward.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear.
What's wrong, Cooper?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not sure
I have a dominant leg.
(Sheldon:)They're both pretty submissive.
(Howard:)When you're in a
public restroom,
(Howard:)which foot do you
flush the toilet with?